

PROFILE

Ungku Muhammad Nazmi, Born in Johor Bahru HSA. 23 Feb 1992. I used my excellent interpersonal and communication skills to do the task and learn the new experience in construction.My experience working in IT field since 2013 and almost more than 8 years in IT job.

I quickly adapt to the environment which was not my field of study and stay positive in facing all challenge.

Type of Employment: Full Time Available upon request (can start immediately)

CONTACT

PHONE: +60177193554

LINKEDIN https://my.linkedin.com/in/ungkumuhammad-nazmi-0a4462227

EMAIL: AFINAZMI92@GMAIL.COM

HOBBIES

SPORTS BADMINTON FUTSAL

EXPECTED SALARY MYR 2800-3000

UNGKU MUHAMMAD NAZMI

IT SPECIALIST

EDUCATION

INSTITUTE LATIHAN PERINDUSTRIAN SELANDAR, MELAKA

2011-01 - 2012-12 Malaysian Skills Certificate SKM Application Development - Programming (CGPA 3.1)

Graduation Date: 20 November 2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance, JOHOR

2022

Part Time Job.

IT SUPPORT EXECUTIVE - MarvelSoft Solution SDN BHD, JOHOR BAHRU 2020-05 to 2021-09

Responsible for Hardware , Server , Networking , Installation ,F&B System, POS system, Stocks checking. Repairing and Troubleshooting Networking/Printer/Laptop/Server

IT SUPPORT ENGINEER-Rank Alpha Technologies SDN BHD, JOHOR BAHRU 2019-03 to 2020-02

Responsible for layout, and maintenance of network, installations support Application Database Sql, Sql Scripting, Backup Database / Restore, software components in company and customers' site.Plan, design, analyze, and provide technical support (Security) for data communications network or group of networks.On-side Support Johor - KL

System Analyz - Extreme Network ENT, JOHOR BAHRU 2019-01 to 2018-12

Responsible for installations, layout, and maintenance of network,software components in company and customers' site. Plan, design, analyze, and provide technical support (Security) for data communications network or group of networks. On-Side Support.

L1- IT INFRA SPECIALIST - CRT INSIGHTS SDB BHD, JOHOR BAHRU 2016-02 to 2017-12

On-side Support Johor – Singapore, Responsible for installations, backup, layout, and maintenance of network, software components in company and customers' site. Plan, design, analyze, and provide technical support (Security) for data communications network or group of networks.

IT SUPPORT SPECIALIST - Unit Sains dan ICT Negeri Johor 2012-01 to 2012-06

(LI) I worked as a customer/User service under Reports. I answered calls from customer/User and was trained to manage Computer hardware, Network, Web, Virus, Software, All about I.T's Problem.

SKILLS

